{
    "subject": "Emperor_Zhao_of_Han",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Grand_Empress_Dowager_Shangguan",
    "human_readable": "Emperor Zhao of Han is married to Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9779050946235657,
            "question": "Identify the emperor who was married to Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9667051434516907,
            "question": "What was the relationship between Emperor Zhao of Han and Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9639363884925842,
            "question": "What was the name of the emperor married to Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9610850811004639,
            "question": "Can you name the emperor who married Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9516196250915527,
            "question": "To whom was Emperor Zhao of Han married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9367554187774658,
            "question": "Who is married to Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9306837320327759,
            "question": "Who was the wife of Emperor Zhao of Han?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8331981301307678,
            "question": "What was the marital status of Emperor Zhao of Han?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6748477220535278,
            "question": "Who is known as Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6548653841018677,
            "question": "Who held the title of Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Emperor Zhao of Han is married to Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan.",
            "html": "yago_29252_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is known as Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan?",
            "html": "yago_29252_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the marital status of Emperor Zhao of Han?",
            "html": "yago_29252_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the wife of Emperor Zhao of Han?",
            "html": "yago_29252_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29252_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29252_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29252_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29252_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29252_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29252_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29252_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29252_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29252_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29252_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any more queries! \ud83d\ude0a  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the triple. According to multiple sources (files 46 and 38), Emperor Zhao was married to Lady Shangguan, who later became Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently indicate that Shangguan, also known as Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan or Empress Shangguan, was indeed married to Emperor Zhao of the Han Dynasty. Therefore, the statement that Emperor Zhao of Han is married to Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}